I heard there's a new witness
in your case.
What, do you have a big chance?
You don't need the information
you need from me
about Berdugo anymore?
I still need it.
Will you keep your promise
or not?
I don't have the information
right now,
but I will give it to you.
Since there is no supporting
evidence,
everything Golda said in court
is considered hearsay.
Actually, I think someone
talked to the judge,
which is why the decision
was made.
We've been looking for Golda
for a long time.
I went through a lot
just to make her testify,
and then they'll just
throw it out?
So that's your plan
and Berdugo's.
Everything has a price.
You just need to know how much.
I saw a deactivated account
that links to Theresa.
I just need to pinpoint
the location,
then I'm sure that I will
find it.
My vlogger friend texted.
There's a big scoop.
The vloggers' intention
was entertainment
and educational content,
but what surprised them
was a disgusting sight.
Berdugo's group did that.
If Berdugo catches me,
that's what I'll definitely
end up with.
Just like what happened
to Godfather Diego?
He just disappeared.
What you have to do
is to make sure
that those bodies can't be
connected to us.
One of the bodies
has been identified
through dental records.
It's Major Aglipay, confirmed.
Our contact at the precinct
said that Parak's ashes
and belongings have been given
to relatives.
We have to make sure that Parak
left nothing behind.
I just remembered our employee
asking for help.
I want to meet her as soon
as possible.
I saw it on the sleeve
of Godfather Diego's jacket.
What are we going to do
with that?
Mom, I think that's the evidence
I'm looking for.
Why did you just tell me now?
Let's go after Chief!
Let's give it to him!
-What?
- No, Mom.
I've learned my lesson.
We need to see what's inside
before we surrender.
Peter, just tell Joey that...
I'm sorry.
I won't make it tonight.
Because I found Theresa's
possible location
based on the IP address.
Yes, from the phone that I got
from Liza's date.
I'm checking it out now.
I'll call you back.
Are you really here, Theresa?
Peter, what took you so long?
I've been waiting for you
for some time now.
Where is Jin Ho?
Why aren't you with him?
Nothing.
Wait, why did you send me here?
Andrew is there.
Threatened?
I want us to be complete
before I open what I found.
Okay.
Found?
This...
Joey found it in Major Aglipay's
belongings.
I saw it on the sleeve
of Godfather Diego's jacket.
I think he really meant
to leave it there
because what's inside
is important.
I wonder what it is.
Maybe some evidence or a list of
names of those in the syndicate.
Let's just find out.
This is just a video file.
Okay, let's watch it.
And you really planning on
running away from us?
No, Lisa, no!
I really came here!
That's it!
That's the video
that will free Father!
Wait, let's rewind this.
Loloy, check what that is.
Maybe this is what your Korean
friend is saying.
Theresa.
But I haven't really
seen her yet.
Joey, I think this is really the
solution to your father's case.
You are going to be
with him very, very soon.
Thank God.
Thanks to all of you.
Oh my, I can't contain my joy.
I want to celebrate.
But, I'm scared.
I might jinx it.
Maybe I'll just celebrate
when Father is really free.
Also, to make it complete,
Jin Ho should be here.
Because I can't do this
on my own.
This only happened because
of the three of you.
Thank you very much.
Okay, I'll call Attorney
to give this to him,
our evidence.
We have to make sure
that it won't be dismissed.
Like what happened
with Golda's testimony.
I have an idea.
We gave the video to your
lawyer,
and he said that it's very
strong for your case.
He also said that he's already
going through the evidence
so that he can give it
to the court.
And he's making sure that
the evidence won't be dismissed
like what happened with Golda's
statement.
So just a little bit, Father,
you can go home.
We'll be together again.
I can't believe it.
Is what I'm hearing true?
Me too.
When the evidence first
landed in my hands,
I thought to myself...
Maybe even though
Godfather Diego is gone,
he wants to make amends with us.
He wants to help us.
Maybe that's why the last time
we met,
it was like he wanted
to tell me something.
Maybe this is it.
He hid the video
because he knew it would be the
one that would set you free.
Maybe you're right.
You know,
I believe that Diego was only
torn with the situation.
And he did this because he wants
to protect me.
He's probably trying to keep me
from getting killed
by the syndicate.
But it's just sad that our
friendship has come to this.
Jin Ho!
What happened?
Did you catch Theresa? Jin Ho!
Not yet, but I know I'm close.
That's nice.
Me too, I have good news
for you too.
What?
Joey found the video.
You know,
the broken USB flash drive.
There's a copy.
- Really? Where?
- Yeah.
Joey? She's visiting her father.
I mean, the video, where is it?
The video...
Joey sent it to the attorney
for evidence.
Ma'am Yvette.
Hey, Clarissa, I've been looking
for you for a while.
I'm sorry.
I was just fixing up
the conference room.
It was used earlier.
You're really hardworking.
That's why it's not too hard
for me to help you.
That's why we're going
to help you now.
This is my husband.
Tomas, Clarissa.
Nice to meet you.
I heard that you need help
with your husband's case.
That's why I told my wife that
I wanted to meet you in person.
Yes, but I don't want
to bother you anymore.
Because my husband's case
is getting stronger.
What do you mean?
There's a new evidence
that has just come out.
What evidence?
Later, make sure our cargo
is ready, so...
What? Did you find it?
I knew it.
You're not going
to keep your word.
There you go again,
you're too excited.
Didn't I say I'd give it to you?
That's it.
You know,
I need to see Berdugo because
he owes Diego and me big time.
Okay.
Okay, I'll tell you.
Are you ready to know?
I'm sorry, because our lawyer
said not to talk
about the latest developments
in my husband's case.
Sorry.
Look.
You asked for my help
but how can I do
that if I don't know the facts?
You can trust me.
Maybe, we don't need
to know anymore, Hon.
We just need to understand
Clarissa.
Of course, she doesn't want to
jeopardize her husband's case.
I understand.
Well, I wish the best for you
and your husband, Clarissa.
Thank you, Sir. I'm sorry.
Excuse me, Hon.
I just have to make a call.
Okay.
Just step aside.
There was an encounter
on Godfather's birthday,
that's why his reputation
was ruined.
He looked weak,
and that's the opportunity
Berdugo has been waiting
for to penetrate the North.
You know, until now,
you still haven't told me
where I can find Berdugo.
If you want to see him,
he'll be meeting with his
new business partners
at the end of the month.
New business partners?
Where will they meet?
Matias, Lisa...
Delgado has a new evidence.
Find out what that is. Hurry up!
Hey.
Where's Joey?
Joey's not here.
She went to visit her Father.
But Golda's upstairs. Why?
You're the one that I need
sto talk to.
Okay.
About what?
The video evidence.
You know, the one with Theresa's
face on it...
Are you going to release it
to the public?
Yeah,
this is the only way to make
sure that the court accepts it
as evidence for Joey's Father.
Which means Theresa
will be exposed too.
She'll be a wanted woman.
Then the police will try
to find her.
Isn't that good for you?
I mean, now you have the
authorities,
and they can help you find her.
You know what?
I think it's best for you
to like to coordinate
- with the police.
- No, no, no, no.
I should be the one to find her.
How come?
You know what,
I have no idea why it has
to be you to catch Theresa,
but I'm sorry.
This is Joey's last hope
to help her father.
I have to release the video.
From the video evidence found
in Major Aglipay's belongings,
it looks like someone else
was involved
in the death of Ramon Orbos.
The question now, Ka-Tirada ...
What will happen to the case
of Major Miguel Delgado,
who was first accused
of killing Ramon Orbos?
Okay, shout out to Janice,
to Bailey, and...
Raven, yes.
Thank you for watching.
Lance and, Osmond.
Yes, yes, thank you.
Judge, we have a favor to ask
from you.
I know what you want to happen,
but I can't ignore
the new evidence.
The video is out
on social media.
It's even gone viral.
They might come back to me
if I don't accept the evidence.
It'll jeopardize my position,
and I will not allow that.
Sorry, my hands are tied.
What?
Did the Judge get it?
Boss, he didn't accept it.
I didn't force it either.
He might get pissed off,
and we'll be at the losing end.
Ready, Boss?
Ready?
We're going live in three,
two, one...
Due to the evidence
that came out
in the case of Major
Miguel Delgado,
the court has made a decision,
Ka-Tiradas .
The former police officer
has been proven innocent.
And now, the police force
is looking for the alias Loloy
and the woman with him
in the video evidence.
So for more information
about the case, Ka-Tiradas ,
Just check the information
below.
Just click the link.
I would like to apologize
to you, Ka-Tiradas ,
And especially to the Delgado
family,
if they were victims
of this fake news.
It just goes to show
that any of us
can be vulnerable to deception.
So let's not just believe what
others say, Ka-Tiradas .
We should be critical,
more meticulous,
and most of all, we should not
stop until the truth comes out.
That smells good, Mom.
Your father will definitely
like this.
- Hello! Is it okay?
- My husband is handsome!
Hey, that's a lot!
We won't be able to finish it.
Gosh.
Are you sure?
Everything we prepared
is your favorite.
I'm sure you miss it so much.
Yes, Father.
And do you know how early Mother
and I woke up
to go shopping and cook?
Wait, wait, wait.
I thought I was free?
Yes.
It's like you're going
to hang me.
- Hey, you're too much.
- No, there's so much of it.
- But that looks delicious.
- Of course.
But of course, it's even better,
I'd be eating with you.
You know, thank you so much
for not giving up on me.
Especially you, Joey.
You really did everything
to so I can be free.
I didn't only feel your love
but also your courage.
So who will your daughter
inherit it from, if not you?
The important thing is,
this problem of ours is over.
And we are far from danger
from now on.
And the most important thing is,
God gave us a second chance.
So we should take care of it?
That's right.
Promise...
I will do everything
so that this doesn't happen
and you don't get hurt again.
That's it.
Thank you.
But, Father...
We still have a lot to thank
because there are so many people
who helped us
so our family would be complete.
Yes. Thank you very much
to them.
If it weren't for them,
we wouldn't be together.
What?
I'm leaving now.
Are you sure?
Where are you going to live?
Do you want me to come with you?
Crazy.
Well, I've found something,
a secluded place.
It's good.
I'll lie low there for now.
Are you safe there?
Yes.
It's better if I leave now
because the movements of
Berdugo's group are restricted.
It's safer.
This.
Take it.
Just a little protection.
Thank you.
Golda, thank you very much
for your help.
What's with you?
I wasn't able to help.
Yes, you did,
you fixed my mother
and father's relationship.
And even though your statement
was not accepted,
I'm still grateful
that you did that.
Good luck.
Be careful.
I'll go ahead.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
I'll take you there.
Why?
You don't want to?
Okay, okay.
Why are you still there?
I thought you were smart.
Get out of there and don't
come back
while the situation
is still hot.
I'm a little hesitant
about Jin Ho's search
for Theresa Park.
You know, I feel like there's
something personal going on
with his search for Theresa.
If you ask me if I go
after what I want.
Then yes.
I will not stop
until she's mine.
Get out!
Do you have any news
about Jin Ho?
Did he come home? No reply yet.
Why don't we interview
Major Miguel Delgado?
Andrew knows a lot about
Delgado,
so I want you to send him
a warning.
Make it loud and make it
personal.
What happened?
What was that?